<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Test for Anger</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="title_which_question">Question %1$d from %2$d</string>
    <string name="start_test">Start test</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="repeat_test">Restart</string>
    <string name="again">Restart</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3820905881551733/9718133002</string>
    <!--<string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>-->


    <string-array name="string_results">
        <item>You are very calm:)</item>
        <item>In general, you are pretty calm:)</item>
        <item>You are the devil in the flesh.:/</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Rate App-->
    <string name="rate_title">Rate Test for Anger</string>
    <string name="rate_message">If you love our app, please take a moment to rate it</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate now</string>
    <string name="rate_no">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="rate_remind">Remind later</string>


    <string name="physic_aggression">Physical aggression</string>
    <string name="indirect_aggression">Indirect aggression</string>
    <string name="temper">Temper</string>
    <string name="negativism">Negativism</string>
    <string name="touchiness">Touchiness</string>
    <string name="suspicion">Suspicion</string>
    <string name="verbal_aggression">Verbal aggression</string>
    <string name="guilt">Guilt</string>

    <string-array name="string_questions">
        <item>If I get angry, I can hit somebody.</item>
        <item>I never get angry enough to throw objects.</item>
        <item>I easily get angry, but quickly calmed down.</item>
        <item>I do not always comply with requests.</item>
        <item>It seems to me that the fate of me is unfair.</item>
        <item>I know that people talk about me behind my back.</item>
        <item>I can not resist the dispute, if people do not agree with me.</item>
        <item>If I happened to deceive anyone, I felt painful remorse.</item>
        <item>It seems to me that I was not able to hit the man.</item>
        <item>When I get angry, then I slam the door.</item>
        <item>Sometimes people just annoy me with their presence.</item>
        <item>If I do not like a rule set, I want to break it.</item>
        <item>Sometimes I envy gnaws at, although I do not show.</item>
        <item>I think many people do not like me.</item>
        <item>I demand that people respect my rights.</item>
        <item>Sometimes I come to mind thoughts, which I am ashamed.</item>
        <item>I know people who can bring me to a fight.</item>
        <item>Sometimes I express the anger that banging his fist on the table.</item>
        <item>I often feel like a powder keg ready to explode.</item>
        <item>If someone poses as a chief, I am always doing it in defiance.</item>
        <item>None of the people I really would hate.</item>
        <item>Quite a lot of people envy me.</item>
        <item>Even if I am angry, I do not resort to "strong" expressions.</item>
        <item>People who shirk work, should feel guilty.</item>
        <item>I rarely going to fight, even if someone hit me.</item>
        <item>I can remember the case when I was so angry that he grabbed the first available object and broke it.</item>
        <item>I am rude towards people who do not like me.</item>
        <item>When talking with me commanding tone, I do not want to do.</item>
        <item>I usually try to hide a bad attitude towards people.</item>
        <item>Sometimes it seems to me that people laugh at me.</item>
        <item>If someone annoys me, I am ready to say what I think about him.</item>
        <item>It depresses me what I am not doing enough for my parents.</item>
        <item>If someone hit me first, I did not answer him.</item>
        <item>When I m disputing, I often raise my voice.</item>
        <item>I do not get angry over small things.</item>
        <item>When people from pretending themselves superior, I do all that they are not conceited.</item>
        <item>I don not always get something good, that I deserve.</item>
        <item>I do not have enemies who want to harm me.</item>
        <item>I often threaten people, but not going to result in the threat of execution.</item>
        <item>I do a lot of this, as later regret.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
